Guide to the McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection, 1980s-1990s and undated RL.00863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Videotapes, 1980s-1990s, 49 boxes
  - 654. Reel for New York. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Hilton: Great American Summer (Box 43)
    - El Pollo Loco: Warning (Box 43)
    - Winchell's: Super Donut (Box 43)
    - Hilton--Chicago: O'Hare (Box 43)
    - Hilton: Anchorage (Box 43)
    - Hilton: Brown (Box 43)
  - 655. Drive Account Showreel. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Nescafé: Welcome/Art School (Japan) (Box 43)
    - Nescafé Decaf: Natural (USA) (Box 43)
    - Chevrolet Pickup: Train Tracks (Mexico) (Box 43)
    - Opel Corsa: Car as Horse (Spain) (Box 43)
    - Esso: Tiger/Erupting Oil Rig (France) (Box 43)
    - Kodak: First Step (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Camel: Statue (Italy) (Box 43)
    - Black & Decker Dustbuster: Birdcage (France) (Box 43)
    - Martini Bianco: Changing Perspectives (Box 43)
    - Swatch Watches: French Fashion (Switzerland) (Box 43)
    - Levi's: A Feeling/Living/Legend (Canada) (Box 43)
    - Coca-Cola: 9 to 5 (Australia) (Box 43)
    - Coca-Cola: Sizzle (International) (Box 43)
    - Cherry Coke: Elevator/Punk (USA) (Box 43)
    - Tiger Beer: Pouring (Box 43)
    - Castlemaine Beer: Workers (Australia) (Box 43)
    - Loburg Beer: Shadows (Belgium) (Box 43)
    - Alka Seltzer: Three Alarm Chili (USA) (Box 43)
    - Sony Watchman TV: King Kong (USA) (Box 43)
    - IMEC: Bride (Italy) (Box 43)
    - Milk: Pole Vaulter (USA) (Box 43)
    - Eiser hosiery: Mystery/Intrigue (Finland) (Box 43)
    - Finn Crystal: Glasses (Finland) (Box 43)
    - Community Chest: Signing Mime (Singapore) (Box 43)
    - Ministry of Transport: Buckle Up/Little David (New Zealand) (Box 43)
    - Stand Up for Singapore: 25 Years of Nation Building (Singapore) (Box 43)
  - 656. Presentation Reel. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [Multinational executions to advertise the same product in different countries.]
    - Domestos disinfectant: Launch (Italy) (Box 43)
    - Domestos disinfectant: Launch (Japan) (Box 43)
    - Domestos disinfectant: Launch (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Domestos disinfectant: Launch (Australia) (Box 43)
    - Domestos disinfectant: 1979 (France) (Box 43)
    - Domestos disinfectant: 1979 Letters (France) (Box 43)
    - Shield soap: Reporter (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Rexona soap: Female Reporter (Italy) (Box 43)
    - Rexona soap: Female Reporter (Spain) (Box 43)
    - Sunlight dish detergent: Reflections (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Sunlight dish detergent: Reflections (South Africa) (Box 43)
    - Svelto dish detergent: Teaspoon (Italy) (Box 43)
    - Sunlight dish detergent: Lemon Power (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Sunlight dish detergent: Casserole (Malaysia) (Box 43)
    - Sunlight dish detergent: Bad Film (Thailand) (Box 43)
    - Sunlight dish detergent: Lemons (USA) (Box 43)
    - Cif liquid cleaner: Recommended Film (France) (Box 43)
    - Cif liquid cleaner: Bath (France) (Box 43)
    - Jif liquid cleaner: Bath (Holland) (Box 43)
    - Jif liquid cleaner: Bath (Austria) (Box 43)
    - Handy liquid cleaner: Launch (South Africa) (Box 43)
    - Vim liquid cleaner: 1 (Canada) (Box 43)
    - Vim liquid cleaner: 2 (Canada) (Box 43)
    - Jif liquid cleaner: Finger (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: New Full Drawer (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: New Full Drawer (Brazil) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: Close (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: Towel (Brazil) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: Close (South Africa) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: Wrap Around (Australia) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: Cross Section (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: Silky Smooth (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Comfort fabric softener: Memories (U.K.) (Box 43)
    - Andy floor cleaner: Explosion (Finland) (Box 43)
    - Vim floor cleaner: Bubbling Water (Chile) (Box 43)
    - Vim floor cleaner: Dancer (Brazil) (Box 43)
    - Vim floor cleaner: Fist (Italy) (Box 43)
    - Vim floor cleaner: Fist (Spain) (Box 43)
    - Omo laundry detergent: S. Maga (Austria) (Box 43)
    - Omo laundry detergent: Hidden Pack (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Omo laundry detergent: MMR (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Omo laundry detergent: Schworer (Switzerland) (Box 43)
    - All laundry detergent: Relaunch (Holland) (Box 43)
    - Lux Beauty Soap: Sophia Loren (International) (Box 43)
    - Lux Beauty Soap: Jaya Sudha (India) (Box 43)
    - Lux Beauty Soap: Parvit Babi (India) (Box 43)
    - Lux Beauty Soap: M. Gardiner (El Salvador) (Box 43)
    - Lux Beauty Soap: Jacqueline Bisset (El Salvador) (Box 43)
    - Lux Beauty Soap: Jacqueline Bisset (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Superwheel laundry detergent: Sound of Music (Philippines) (Box 43)
    - Superwheel laundry detergent: Nero (Philippines) (Box 43)
    - Superwheel laundry detergent: Robin Hood (Philippines) (Box 43)
    - Koral laundry detergent: Cartoon (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Koral laundry detergent: Dancers (Finland) (Box 43)
    - Koral laundry detergent: Comparison (Austria) (Box 43)
    - Koral laundry detergent: Comparison (Switzerland) (Box 43)
    - Koral laundry detergent: Designer (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Koral laundry detergent: Designer (Belgium) (Box 43)
    - Skip laundry detergent: Swimmers (France) (Box 43)
    - Skip laundry detergent: Split Screen (France) (Box 43)
    - Skip laundry detergent: Split Screen (France) (Box 43)
    - Omo laundry detergent: Miele MMR (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Omo laundry detergent: TAED (Germany) (Box 43)
    - Omo laundry detergent: TAED (Switzerland) (Box 43)
    - All laundry detergent: TAED (Holland) (Box 43)
    - Lux beauty soap: Michelle Pfeiffer Car (International) (Box 43)
    - Lux beauty soap: Michelle Pfeiffer Car (International) (Box 43)
    - Lux beauty soap: Michelle Pfeiffer Boat (International) (Box 43)
    - Lux beauty soap: Michelle Pfeiffer Boat (International) (Box 43)
  - 657. Bill Mount (writer/creative director). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [See also Tape 658]
    - Taco Bell: Pizzazz Pizza Intro 1 (Box 43)
    - Budweiser: Newspaper (Box 43)
    - Mercantile Bank: Undisciplined (Box 43)
    - Taco Bell: Campaign intro (Box 43)
    - Michelob Light: Darts (Box 43)
    - Doritos: Definitely intro (Box 43)
    - Taco Bell: Nachos Gotcha (Box 43)
    - Michelob Light: Volleyball (Box 43)
    - Doritos: Son of Definitely (Box 43)
    - Taco Bell: Pizzazz Pizza 2 (Box 43)
    - Doritos: The Wall/Painted Brick Wall (Box 43)
    - Pepsi: Let's Go to the Movies (Box 43)
  - 658. Bill Mount. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [See also Tape 657]
    - Taco Bell: Pizzazz Pizza Intro 1 (Box 43)
    - Budweiser: Newspaper (Box 43)
    - Mercantile Bank: Undisciplined (Box 43)
    - Taco Bell: Campaign intro (Box 43)
    - Michelob Light: Darts (Box 43)
    - Doritos: Definitely intro (Box 43)
    - Taco Bell: Nachos Gotcha (Box 43)
    - Michelob Light: Volleyball (Box 43)
    - Doritos: Son of Definitely (Box 43)
    - Taco Bell: Pizzazz Pizza 2 (Box 43)
    - Doritos: The Wall/Painted Brick Wall (Box 43)
    - Pepsi: Let's Go to the Movies (Box 43)
  - 659. Scali McCabe Sloves, Nikon One Touch Camera. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Nikon One Touch Camera: Tourist (Box 43)
  - 660. Charlie; Armourcoat. 1980. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 2:30 (Box 44)
    - Charlie: After the Party (Box 44)
    - Armourcoat II: Non-Stick Cookware (Box 44)
  - 661. Ritz; Goodyear; Esso. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 44)
    [Discussion of R.J. Reynolds/Nabisco merger and how Nabisco was then subject to the RJR transnational marketing/advertising scheme. The marketing strategy behind expanding Ritz's market including: The Wizard of Ritz; The Ritz Baker; The Magician; and The Professor. Alternate strategies are also covered: Irresistible Taste; Nature's Gold; and Ritz It Up. Goodyear International Advertising: The strategy had to be simple and all-encompassing, an emotional evocation--discusison about different strategies behind Goodyear, Take Me Home. The people approach; the panorama approach. Esso: Several projects that the Esso campaign is dealing with. The Tiger Project--the future use of the tiger. The Brazilian campaign--they want to abolish the old advertising and use something completely new.]
  - 662. Seledmaier Reel. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Alaska Airlines: Automatons (Box 44)
    - Hormel: Car (Box 44)
    - Valvoline: Parade (Box 44)
    - Check-Up: Taxi (Box 44)
    - Fiberglas: Flamingos (Box 44)
    - Alaska Airlines: Winter (Box 44)
    - Check-Up: Executive Washroom (Box 44)
    - Nike: Ladies (Box 44)
    - Wendy's: 12 O'Clock (Box 44)
    - Alaska Airlines: TV Viewer (Box 44)
    - On Cor Lite: No Imitations (Box 44)
    - Tank n' Bowl: Ed (Box 44)
    - Alaska Airlines: Cutting Corners (Box 44)
    - GMAC: Hassle Free (Box 44)
    - Wendy's: Moustache (Box 44)
    - Fiberglas: Pool Party (Box 44)
    - Happy Cooker: History of Gas (Box 44)
    - Valvoline: Funeral (Box 44)
    - Independent Life: Department Store (Box 44)
    - Alaska Airlines: Conference Room (Box 44)
    - Europassistance: Car (Box 44)
    - Europassistance: Plumber (Box 44)
    - Check-Up: Airplane (Box 44)
    - Subaru: Schiminson (Box 44)
    - Wendy's: Farm Fresh (Box 44)
    - Fiberglas: Edna (Box 44)
    - GMAC: Auto-Teller (Box 44)
    - Wendy's: Fashion Show (Box 44)
  - 663. Slice-of-Life (Take Off On Sit Coms): Wisk, Anacin 3, Playtex Tampon, Dawn, Halls, Amana. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Wisk: Ring Around the Collar/TV & Home (Box 44)
    - Anacin 3: Office Testimony (Box 44)
    - Playtex Tampon: Talk with Mom (Box 44)
    - Dawn: Sorority House (Box 44)
    - Hall's: Camping Trip (Box 44)
    - Amana: Discussion (Box 44)
  - 664. TV Register. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Maxwell House High: Brazilian Mountains (Box 44)
    - Maxwell House Mountain Blend: Train (Box 44)
    - Wm. Younger's Tartan beer: Highland Games (Box 44)
    - Smithwick's beer: Airport (Box 44)
    - Whitbread Best Scotch: Business Meeting (Box 44)
    - Autumn Gold Cider: Falling Things (Box 44)
    - Harvey's Finesse Sherry: Untraditional (Box 44)
    - Volari Wine: Friends at Bar (Box 44)
    - XXX Beer: Extraterrestrial (Box 44)
    - Dwan's: Good Drinks (Box 44)
    - Tudor Crisps: Nothing Seemed Real (Box 44)
    - Phileas Fogg chips: Cruise Ship (Box 44)
    - Vesta Chow Mein: Oriental Scenes (Box 44)
    - Beanfeast: Calendar (Box 44)
    - Bird's Eye Country Club Vegetables: Country Club (Box 44)
    - Ungor's King Ribs: Melting Silver (Box 44)
    - Butterball Turkey Breast Roast: Jack Spratt (Box 44)
    - Quaker's Golden Oates: Ships (Box 44)
    - Crosse & Blackwell Pasta Choice: Real Italian (Box 44)
    - Hammond's Chop Sauce: Chop Shaped Food (Box 44)
    - Creda Oven: Role Reversal (Box 44)
    - Addis Housewares: Art Gallery (Box 44)
    - Hoover Sensotronic: Spilled Flour (Box 44)
    - Potterton Boilers: This Old House (Box 44)
    - Laing: New Home (Box 44)
    - Pifco Vacuum Bag Sealer: Fresh Food (Box 44)
    - Punch Shoeshine: Quick (Box 44)
    - Zenith Windows: Cat (Box 44)
    - Calor Gas: Village Idiot (Box 44)
    - Savlon Germ Killer: She's a Killer (Box 44)
    - Grundig Electronics: Tunnel Car (Box 44)
    - ITT Computerized TV: Computer TV (Box 44)
    - Philips: Color Balance (Box 44)
    - Mitsubishi Blue Diamond: Blue Screen (Box 44)
    - Radio Rentals: Desert Snow (Box 44)
    - Ocean Rain--Echo and the Bunnymen promo (Box 44)
    - Stinky Stickers: Scratch-n-Sniff (Box 44)
    - Flower Fairies dolls: Fantasyland (Box 44)
    - A La Carte Kitchen: Play Kitchen (Box 44)
    - Hasbro Knight Rider: Toy Car Set (Box 44)
    - Shield Soap: Jewel Thief (Box 44)
    - Fairy Soap: 2 Statues (Box 44)
    - Moncler Derma Soap: Mirror (Box 44)
    - Simple Cold Cream: Additives (Box 44)
    - Disprin: Family Headaches (Box 44)
    - Boots Soluble Aspirin: Mug (Box 44)
    - Phillshave Electronic: Sale (Box 44)
    - Lumière perfume: First Light (Box 44)
    - Givenchy Ysatis perfume: Looking For (Box 44)
    - Cacharel cologne: Desert/Cars (Box 44)
    - The Sunday Times: Hugh Hefner Story (Box 44)
    - The Guardian: Richard Branson (Box 44)
    - Daily Express/Sunday Express/Daily Star: Million Pounds (Box 44)
    - Sunday Telegraph: H.G. Wells (Box 44)
    - The Observer: Britons Observed (Box 44)
    - Al Ahram: International Edition (Box 44)
    - Debut Magazine: Rock Mag (Box 44)
    - UBM Building Supplies: Man/Train (Box 44)
    - Weekender clothes: Race Cars (Box 44)
    - Leeds Liquid Gold Account: Gold Bars (Box 44)
    - Abby National: Sky Lift (Box 44)
    - Woolwich Bank: With It (Box 44)
    - ICS Building Society: Hang Glider (Box 44)
    - The Principality: Excited (Box 44)
    - Style Card: Images on a Card (Box 44)
    - Barclay Card: French Alps (Box 44)
    - Persil Products: Free Train Ticket (Box 44)
    - British Telecom: Let's Go to the Shop (Box 44)
    - Economy 7 Electric Water Heater: Hot Bath (Box 44)
    - Deliotte, Haskins & Sells accountants: Removing Restrictions (Box 44)
    - Peterborough: Gladiator (Box 44)
    - Apple Macintosh: Best Pick (Box 44)
    - Bank of Ireland: Free Carot (Box 44)
    - Capital Radio: Are You Ready (Box 44)
    - Lion Brand Stationery: Rock Concert (Box 44)
    - Olivetti Word Processors: Truck (Box 44)
    - Canon Copiers: Swimming Pool (Box 44)
    - BAT Industries: Growing (Box 44)
    - Leyland Roadrunner: Desert (Box 44)
    - Ford Transit: Rescue (Box 44)
    - BMW 3 Series: Satellite Dish (Box 44)
    - Volkswagen Jetta: One of Those (Box 44)
    - Vauxhall Nova: Subway (Box 44)
    - Stratstone Jaguar: Greenline Jaguar (Box 44)
    - Ski Club 1830: Skiing (Box 44)
    - British Midland: Airport (Box 44)
    - Cathay Pacific Airlines: Hostesses (Box 44)
    - Qantas Business Class Flights: Koala Bear (Box 44)
    - Granvilles cigars: Courtroom (Box 44)
    - Crown Paints: Merry Go Round (Box 44)
    - Toshiba Deltawave microwave: Dinner Party (Box 44)
    - Phillips Pet Food: Pet Care Book (Box 44)
    - Cadbury's: Million Pound Giveaway (Box 44)
    - Mobil: Monopoly Game (Box 44)
    - Dime candy bar: Muted Sound (Box 44)
    - Maltesers chocolate candy: Beach (Box 44)
  - 665. TV Register. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 44, Video-cassette RL00863-UM-0006, Digital-materials RL00863-SET-0001, Video-file RL00863-UM-0006.mov)
    - Melitta Coffee: Cartoon Bean (Box 44)
    - Nescafé Gold Blend: Gold Standard (Box 44)
    - Douwe Egberts Coffee: Years of Making (Box 44)
    - Choicest Blends Tea: Secret (Box 44)
    - Tennent's Lager: Juke Box (Box 44)
    - Bank's Bitter: Time Traveler (Box 44)
    - Greene King IPA Bitter: Masters of the Art (Box 44)
    - Craft Original Sherry: Yachting (Box 44)
    - Piermont: Hint of Fruit (Box 44)
    - Kiri Apple Juice: Apple Bomb (Box 44)
    - Heinz Homestyle Soups: Sailor (Box 44)
    - Batchelors Soups: Mums/Heroes (Box 44)
    - Colman's Sauces: Male Cook (Box 44)
    - Homepride Cook-in-Sauce: Animated Butter (Box 44)
    - Bovril coffee product: Chris Evert (Box 44)
    - Kit Kat: Anglo-Soviet Talks (Box 44)
    - Toffifee candy: Addam's Family Parody (Box 44)
    - HP Sauce: Robot People (Box 44)
    - Wall's Pork Sausages: Home Breakfast (Box 44)
    - Hob-Nobs Cookies: Armor (Box 44)
    - Energy Efficient Office: Winter Preparation (Box 44)
    - Eveready Silver Seal Battery: Longer Lasting (Box 44)
    - Osram Light Bulbs: Arthur Peabody (Box 44)
    - Breville Griller: Singing Grill (Box 44)
    - Hitachi Power Tools: My Wife (Box 44)
    - Murelle Wallpaper: Roll Out a Room (Box 44)
    - Gas Wall Heaters: Winter Cold (Box 44)
    - Swan Vestas: Computer Screen (Box 44)
    - Persil laundry detergent: Don't Worry (Box 44)
    - Sony Trinitron TV: Man's Life (Box 44)
    - Toshiba TV: Talking Diagram (Box 44)
    - Normende TV: Red Swimsuit (Box 44)
    - Philips VHS Video: Duck (Box 44)
    - Ferguson TX TV: Today's Technology (Box 44)
    - DER Rental: that's DER (Box 44)
    - CBS Child Guidance Toys: Mission to Earth (Box 44)
    - The Age of Consent--Bronski Beat promo (Box 44)
    - Eliminator--ZZ Top promo (Box 44)
    - English National Opera: Speaks for Itself (Box 44)
    - Avon: Avon Now (Box 44)
    - Wella Balsam shampoo and conditioners: Busy Model (Box 44)
    - Silvikrin shampoo: Time After Time (Box 44)
    - Scoundrel: Free Gift (Box 44)
    - Scholl Fresh Step: Tap Dancer (Box 44)
    - Comfies Diapers: Child Board Meeting (Box 44)
    - Nurofen pain reliever: Locked in Pain (Box 44)
    - Lockets cold medicine: 2 Miseries (Box 44)
    - Vick's Blue: Tarzan (Box 44)
    - Deep Heat muscle rub: Lightning (Box 44)
    - Sainsbury's groceries: Interviews (Box 44)
    - Marks & Spencer department store: Now Open (Box 44)
    - Dewhurst Meat and Poultry: Sunday Roast (Box 44)
    - Connect Electronics Stores: Graphics (Box 44)
    - Rumbelow's Appliance Store: Slapstick (Box 44)
    - Daily Express/Sunday Express/Daily Star: Millionaire of the Month (Box 44)
    - The Yorkshire Post: Sports/Women (Box 44)
    - A La Carte Magazine: Food (Box 44)
    - City Limits Magazine: No Bingo (Box 44)
    - Time Out Magazine: Empty Room (Box 44)
    - Lloyd's Bank: Spending Interest (Box 44)
    - British Telecom: Urging Offer (Box 44)
    - Leeds Permanent Building Society: Mobsters (Box 44)
    - Newcastle Building Society: Print Out (Box 44)
    - Educational Building Society: Yes Yes Yes (Box 44)
    - TSB Bank: Yes! (Box 44)
    - Postal Service: I'll Miss You (Box 44)
    - American Express: Jim Henson (Box 44)
    - Apricot Portable Computer: Brick Wall (Box 44)
    - Commodore 16: Starter Pack (Box 44)
    - Spectrum Computers: Restyling (Box 44)
    - Compaq Computers: Buried Heads (Box 44)
    - Epson Computers: Morning Business (Box 44)
    - Sagesoft Software: Clown (Box 44)
    - Fire Safety: Night Fire (Box 44)
    - IBM Electronic Typewriter: Nervous (Box 44)
    - Case Electronic Mailbox: Imagine (Box 44)
    - Neighborhood Watch: Birds (Box 44)
    - GM Astra: Unveiling (Box 44)
    - Renault 25: Volcano/Opera (Box 44)
    - Ford Cars: Business Team (Box 44)
    - Peugeot 205: Top Hat (Box 44)
    - Datsun/Nissan: Name Change (Box 44)
    - British International Motor Show: Take a Trip into Tomorrow (Box 44)
    - Air Mauritius: Out of this World (Box 44)
    - Horizon Travel: Mr. Cooper (Box 44)
    - Thompson Holiday: Ski Vacation (Box 44)
    - Royal Dutch Cigars: Movie Car (Box 44)
    - Nilvax 30 sheep disease protection: Falling Sheep (Box 44)
    - Brother Knitting Machine: Photo Session (Box 44)
    - Dunlopillo Beds: Night/Day (Box 44)
    - Bisto Kids: Gravy Boat (Box 44)
    - Boots Soundshop: Michael Jackson (Box 44)
    - Welcome to the Pleasuredome--Frankie Goes to Hollywood promo (Box 44)
    - Allsop 3: Cassette Cleaner (Box 44)
    - Amstrad Stereos: Special Features (Box 44)
    - Kodak Video Tapes: A Lot of Money (Box 44)
  - 666. TV Register. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Schwepp's Ginger Ale: Dallas (Box 44)
    - Barbicon Beer: Airplane Tragedy (Box 44)
    - Holsten Pils beer: Western (Box 44)
    - Carling Black Label Lager: Popeye (Box 44)
    - Bezique: Stop Action (Box 44)
    - Tia Maria liqueur: Model (Box 44)
    - Malibu: Space People (Box 44)
    - Bailey's: Nightclub (Box 44)
    - Gran Marnier: Business Call (Box 44)
    - Cadbury's: Later Tonight (Box 44)
    - Whitbread Trophy Bitter: Dog Disobedience (Box 44)
    - Stone's Bitter: Airport (Box 44)
    - Black Tower: Dancer in White (Box 44)
    - Hirondelle Wine: Weather (Box 44)
    - Young's: Young's Ones (Box 44)
    - Ross Puddings: Skool Kids (Box 44)
    - Solar candy bar: Singing Sun (Box 44)
    - Smarties: Floating Candy (Box 44)
    - Cadbury Hazel Nuts: Carnival Monkeys (Box 44)
    - Meadowcup Spread: Cows (Box 44)
    - McDougall's Flour: Sponge Cakes (Box 44)
    - Bisto Gravy Granules: Tarzan (Box 44)
    - Knorr's Special Recipe Soup: English Mansion (Box 44)
    - Bowyer's Sausage: Fat (Box 44)
    - Mini Cheddars crackers: Singing Mice (Box 44)
    - Crawford's Mini Cookies: Bug Cartoon (Box 44)
    - Tefal Deep Fryer: Comparison/Brains (Box 44)
    - Wilkinson Sword cutlery: Test Pattern (Box 44)
    - Bosch power tools: Jack and Harry (Box 44)
    - Thor washer/dryer: 950XDC Song (Box 44)
    - Ariel laundry detergent: Soccer Mom (Box 44)
    - Mellerware Oven Pan: Steam Words (Box 44)
    - Morphy Richards steam iron: Ironing Horrors (Box 44)
    - Rowenta toasters: Evolving Form (Box 44)
    - Sunbeam deep fryer/slow cooker: Roxie's recipe (Box 44)
    - Samsung microwave: Vincent Price (Box 44)
    - Seiko Sport Tech watch: Manikins (Box 44)
    - Citizen watches: Watch Out (Box 44)
    - Braun Voice Control alarm clock: White Room (Box 44)
    - Kodak Disc Camera: Puzzle (Box 44)
    - Virgin Albums: Rapper (Box 44)
    - Acorn video games: Space Aliens (Box 44)
    - Fisher Price music equipment: Can't Touch (Box 44)
    - Hitachi Prismacolor TV: Computer Technology (Box 44)
    - Ferguson VCR: Best Value (Box 44)
    - VO5 Alive color mousse: Phones (Box 44)
    - Noir aftershave: Sky (Box 44)
    - Gentle Touch by Pond's: Get in Touch (Box 44)
    - Poly High Lights: Walking Women (Box 44)
    - Bic disposable razor: John McEnroe (Box 44)
    - Sorbothane Shock Stoppers: Shoe Support (Box 44)
    - Lofthouse Fisherman's Friend: Ship (Box 44)
    - Comtrex: Fire Eater (Box 44)
    - Tramil 500: Office Noise (Box 44)
    - Vicks Sinex: Seashore (Box 44)
    - Tesco: Gift Packs (Box 44)
    - Littlewoods: Tarzan (Box 44)
    - Harrod's: Christmas Tradition (Box 44)
    - Working Woman: Testimonial (Box 44)
    - Cook's Weekly: Wild Recipe (Box 44)
    - The Fourth Protocol: Hottest Book (Box 44)
    - Guinness Book: Millipede (Box 44)
    - Kwik Fit Auto: Bad Muffler (Box 44)
    - Diamond's: Sky Writer (Box 44)
    - Coopers and Lybrand: Braithwait Oil (Box 44)
    - American Express: Roger Daltrey (Box 44)
    - The Leeds: Red Letter Day (Box 44)
    - Nottingham Buiding Society: TV Access (Box 44)
    - Portman Building Society: Otter (Box 44)
    - Bank of Scotland: Fix-Ups (Box 44)
    - Girobank: Rolling Script (Box 44)
    - Ulster Bank: Henry Hippo (Box 44)
    - Midland Personal Loans: Things to Buy (Box 44)
    - IBA: Consumer Protection (Box 44)
    - Ericsson Personal Computer: Walking Baby (Box 44)
    - Acorn Electron computer: Classroom (Box 44)
    - Micronet computer: Imagination (Box 44)
    - Macintosh: Syntax Error (Box 44)
    - Racal Kodafone: Bicycle for Two (Box 44)
    - Postal Order Gift Card: Choices (Box 44)
    - Cook Electric appliances: Cook Electric (Box 44)
    - IDB--Northern Ireland: Come On… (Box 44)
    - Peter Polain & Associates advertising agency: Remember (Box 44)
    - Team Xerox: Office City (Box 44)
    - Freestyle Travel brochure: 1-2-3 (Box 44)
    - Intercity Sleeper: Moving Motel (Box 44)
    - WTL Travelcard: Do the Hop (Box 44)
    - Bus Travel: Shop on a Bus (Box 44)
    - 1985 Ford Sierra: Family Trip (Box 44)
    - Vauxhall Cavalier: Police (Box 44)
    - Renault II: Avoiding the Traffic (Box 44)
    - Peter England shirts: Out of the Grey (Box 44)
    - Clairol Power Dryer: Hurricane (Box 44)
    - Philishave Electronic: Pedestal (Box 44)
    - Freshbrew Coffee: It Can Happen (Box 44)
    - Terry's Logger candy bar: Country (Box 44)
    - Spania Fruit: Kids (Box 44)
    - Hamlet Cigars: Computer Face (Box 44)
  - 667. TV Register. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - John Smith's Bitter: Incurable Romantic (Box 44)
    - Babycharm Beer: Animal Bar (Box 44)
    - Lilt fruit drink: Reggae (Box 44)
    - Perrier: Glass Close-Up (Box 44)
    - Horlick's: Track (Box 44)
    - Carlberg Lager: Binoculars (Box 44)
    - Greenall's Bitter: Western (Box 44)